# Patrick Ojeh



patrickojeh@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/patrickojeh



+2348038392060



https://patrickojeh.com

# **Summary**

I have over 7 years of digital product design experience for web and mobile interfaces and interactions. I have helped small startups and large organizations deliver functional and visually appealing solutions using a combination of design skills and code.

My competencies include: Product design, UI design & development, CSS architecture, CSS, SCSS, HTML, JavaScript, Front-end development

If you'd like to learn more about me, please send an email (hi@patrickojeh.com)

# **Experience**

## **Senior Product Designer**

Mobnia

Oct 2017 - Present (4 years 5 months +)

At Mobnia, I work with a brilliant team to help solve problems and build solutions for bold businesses looking to make a difference.

# Senior User Interface Engineer

Afrinvest West Africa

Oct 2018 - Dec 2020 (2 years 3 months)

- Afrinvestor is a stock trading and investment mobile application
- I worked as the senior user interface engineer for the hybrid mobile app and the admin CRM web application.
- Some tools and technologies I used here include Figma, Design Thinking, Prototyping, Bootstrap, CSS/SCSS, SASS Architecture, HTML, JavaScript.



## **User Interface Engineer**

#### gbamng

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018 (1 year 1 month)

- · Gbam is a mobile scratch lottery platform
- I worked as the user interface engineer for the scratch lottery mobile app and the admin backend web application.
- Some tools and technologies I used here include Sketch, Design Thinking, Prototyping, Bootstrap, CSS/SCSS, SASS Architecture, HTML, JavaScript.



### **User Interface Engineer**

#### Revova

2015 - 2017 (3 years)

- Revova is an HR SaaS software solution for businesses to better manage their processes, from human management to payroll.

- Designed and developed the user interface a platform
- I used tools such as Figma, Sketch, HTML, CSS/SCSS, Bootstrap, Webpack, etc. to create an exciting interface.

## **Education**

**Udacity** 

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree Jan 2022 - Jan 2022

University of Benin

BSc, Insurance, Banking and Finance

## **Licenses & Certifications**

- HackerRank Skills Verification Test (CSS) HackerRank
- HackerRank Skills Verification Test (Javascript) HackerRank
- CSS Expert Pluralsight
- HTML Expert Pluralsight

## **Skills**

Figma • Product Design • User Interface Design • Design Thinking • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • SASS • HTML • JavaScript • Responsive Web Design • User Interface Prototyping